A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Albums, RG 2 FA1128A FA1128A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Large, 1910 - 1990s; 1
  - 300 - Miscellaneous, 1929-1988; 4
    - 300-4, 1960s-1980s; Mainly color snapshots in fabric covered magnetic album. (Box A 32)
      JY Ranch, Hawaii, Grandchildren, Foreign Visitors at Pocantico. Snapshots, LSR, MFR, JY (Family and grandchildren), Mauna Kea and guests, JY board meetings; Caribbean Sea Star, LSR and MFR; Woodstock family; board meeting or party in Hawaii; LSR, MFR, Happy, DR at Kykuit party for unidentified woman. (LSR Album Accession number 114.)
    - 300-5, 1970s-1980s; Large magnetic album, many photos slipping (Box A 33)
      LSR and MFR guests; at Lady Bird's ranch; Maine: NAR's Sea Star, Eyrie; Woodstock with Lady Bird; Family Christmas at Playhouse; in Caribbean on Sea Star; Woodstock garden; golf; Lady Bird and Last Round-up benefit, 1976 (LSR Album Accession number 193.)
    - 300-6, LSR Nature Photographs, 1973; Square, approx. 8x8 color prints (Box A 33)
      Possibly Hawaii. Photos of land and seascapes, orchids, volcano, jungle, deer or elk (JY); poinsettia. (LSR Album Accession number 189.)
    - 300-7, circa 1977; 3x5 color snapshots, photos slipping (Box A 34)
      JY Ranch, Hudson River, Trip with Lady Bird Johnson, Vermont. LSR at JY; Dauntless at Tarrytown with LSR, MFR, Mrs. Bobst, captains; Woodstock; on board Sea Star. (LSR Album Accession number 116.)
    - 300-8, 1979; Magnetic ring binder in poor condition; 12 photos. Should copy and remove from the album binding (Box A 34)
      LSR, MFR on Island of Delos, Greece, sent by Molly Christal, July 1979; draft horses; band at Woodstock Inn; JY pool and wildlife. (LSR Album Accession number 190.)
    - 300-9, 1979; Flip album, photo cases entirely detached from album pages. 19 color 3x5 snapshots. Cases are grotty - rehouse? (Box A 35)
      French Family reunion; LSR, MFR, Lady Bird with Park Ranger tour; group photos (LSR Album Accession number 117.)
    - 300-10, Mary and Laurance Rockefeller Photographs taken during the Year 1987, Magnetic album, color 4x6 and black and white 8x10s. (Box A 35)
      Visit to Winrock Farm; Family visit to Lakeview Cemetery, Cleveland, 50th anniversary of JDR's death; JDR Family Cemetery, Tarrytown, NY, May 30, 1987, including Fannie Evans and Mary Hogan stones; Japanese House, Pocantico, gardens; LSR Princeton honorary degree; 1987 Christmas card photo of JY; Visit to Peggy and David's farm in Hudson valley, October. (LSR Album Accession number 227.) Album compiled by Ruth Haupert.
    - LSR Photographs and Photographic Themes: Travel and Miscellaneous, Art Objects, Caribbean Scenery and Flowers, Undated, 1930s-1980s; Ring bound magnetic pages; color and black and white; photos by LSR (Box A 36)
      Animals and wildlife, including the Mazes's puppies, pets; Art: 834, Pocantico, parks, JY; Caribbean, Flowers, Hawaii, Mexico, Egypt, Africa; Dauntless; NY views, China; Woodstock and film crew; several early JY photos, including MFR (honeymoon) and Wyoming landscape.
    - Reception following Memorial Service for Mrs. George Hinman, 1988 October; 9 color 4x6 snapshots in large magnetic album. Remove to folder. (Box A 35)
      LSR, MFR, Happy Rockefeller, (George Hinman).
  - 400 - Civic, 1950-1990; 5
    - 400-1, Proposed Virgin Islands National Park, 1950s; Leather ring bound album with professional black and white 8x10 photos. Text and captions are coming unglued from the pages. (Box A 37)
      Landscape and features, with text taken from booklet published by National Park Service. Includes picture of LSR, Henry Beebe, Frank Stick, Julius Sprauve, Reverend Starling. (LSR Album Accession number 118.)
    - 400-2, Dedication Virgin Islands National Park, St. John, 1956 December 1; Black and white 8x10 photos in ring-bound album, followed by clippings and copies of selected documents (Box A 37)
      Ceremonies and celebration; LSR and board. (LSR Album Accession number 119.)
    - 400-3, Meeting of the Board of Directors, Eastern Air Lines, Inc., June 5, 1959, San Juan, P.R., and Caneel Bay Plantation, 1959 June; Captioned black and white 8x10 photos, in Accopress binder (Box A 38)
      Dorado Beach Hotel and Caneel Bay. Includes Eddie Rickenbacker, LSR. (LSR Album Accession number 120.)
    - 400-4, Meeting of the Board of Directors, Eastern Air Lines, Inc., Flamingo, Everglades National Park, 1959 October 2; Captioned black and white 8x10 photos, in page protectors, held with prong clips. (Box A 38)
      Includes LSR, Eddie Rickenbacker. (LSR Album Accession number 121.)
    - 400-5, Eastern Air Lines Board, Argentina, 1982 November 5-7; Color snapshots (Box A 39)
      LSR Album Accession number 191.
    - 400-6, Presentation of the Report of the ORRRC to President Kennedy, White House, 1962 January 31; Black and white 8x10 photos (Box A 39)
      LSR Album Accession number 122.
    - 400-7, YWCA Reception in honor of the Commissioners General of the New York World's Fair, 1964 April 28; In vinyl ring binder with sticky cover. Black and white 8x10 photos (Box A 40)
      Hosted by Mrs. Ethan Allen Hitchcock and Mrs. LSR. Includes guest list document. (LSR Album Accession number 210.)
    - 400-8, Lady Bird Johnson "To Mary and Laurance with Happy Memories of the Grand Tetons", 1965 September 7-10; Red leather ringbinder album with embossed title. Cover detached and sticky. Color 8x10 photos. (Box A 40)
      LSR Album Accession number 123.
    - 400-9, Lady Bird Johnson, LSR, and White House Conference on Natural Beauty, 1965 May; Oversized album with captioned 9x12 color prints (Box A 41)
      Album on Natural Beauty Conference projects, created by Lady Bird for LSR (LSR Album Accession number 125.)
    - 400-10, The Hill Country of Texas, 1966 May; Oversized Leather album with captioned 8x10 color prints (Box A 42)
      Presentation album from Lady Bird and LBJ to LSR and MFR commemorating their visit to Texas, May 14, 1966. Includes two undated notes from Lady Bird to LSR and MFR, thanking them for (Beautification) Committee work in Washington, DC, and for portrait of Madison by Vanderlyn, which they gave for the White House. (LSR Album Accession number 124.)
    - 400-11, Valley of the Seven Sacred Pools. Kipahulu, Maui, Hawaii., 1967 December; 9 8x10 color prints; binder mislabeled 1969 (Box A 43)
      Presentation album to MFR and LSR of waterfalls in the park, from Jean and Ham McCaughey, Kipahulu Cattle Company, December 19, 1967. (LSR Album Accession number 126.)
    - 400-12, Brinkerhoff House Reception, September 16, 1972. JDR Jr. Memorial Parkway Dedication, September 18, 1972., 1972 September; 8x10 color prints (Box A 43)
      Ring bound presentation album; list of captions included to identify persons in photographs. (LSR Album Accession number 127.)
    - 400-13, LSR and MFR visit to LBJ Ranch, 1969; Professional 8 x 10 and 11 x 13 color prints (Box A 44)
      Prints dated May 1969. Lady Bird, LSR, MFR, wildflowers, LSR holding portrait of LBJ, exhibit on LBJ, construction of LBJ library. (LSR Album Accession number 128.)
    - 400-14, Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 1971; Oversized, mainly color prints 11x13 (Box A 44)
      Dedication. LBJ and Lady Bird, Richard and Pat Nixon. Captioned by Lady Bird for LSR and MFR (LSR Album Accession number 129.)
    - 400-15, "To Mary and Laurance Rockefeller with gratitude and affection from Lady Bird Johnson and the many people of all ages who will enjoy 'The Overlook,' October 7, 1972.", Color 4x6 and 8x10 photos. Leather album cover sticky and deteriorated. (Box A 45)
      LBJ Library landscaping and grounds, with some captions, and Lady Bird diary excerpt, November 12, 1968. Includes letters from Lady Bird to LSR and MFR, December 20, 1971, and November 6, 1972. (LSR Album Accession number 130.)
    - 400-16, Dedication of Kawaihae Village (Pu'ukohola Heiau National Historic Site), Hawaii, 1972 November 4; Black and white and color photos, mainly 5x7. Newspaper clippings. Magnetic album, some pages coming apart, but items are glued to pages. (Box A 46)
      Scrapbook with clippings and photos; LSR spoke at ceremonies. (LSR Album Accession number 180.)
    - 400-17, Dedication of Spelman Halls, Princeton University, 1973; Black and white 5 x 7 photos, 1 color 8x10, in oversized album (Box A 47)
      Ceremonies and buildings, LSR and MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 131.)
    - 400-18, Spelman Halls, Princeton University, 1973; Color and black and white photos in large album. (Box A 48)
      Pictorial album of Spelman Halls exteriors, sent by builders, Lewis C. Bowers and Sons, to LSR, April 15, 1974. (LSR Album Accession number 132.)
    - 400-19, United Neighborhood Houses 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1975 June; Ring binder, 8x10 black and white photos. (Box A 49)
      Honoring Astor and Rockefeller families, June 3, 1975, NY. Includes LSR, Brooke Astor, Lady Bird, Jesse Jackson, etc. (LSR Album Accession number 133.)
    - 400-20, "Last Round-Up" Benefit (barbecue) at LBJ Ranch, 1976 December; Album binder deteriorating (cover lining detaching) (Box A 49)
      Lady Bird, LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 134.)
    - 400-21, LBJ Memorial Grove groundbreaking and dedication, 1974, 1976; Color snapshots in stacked flip album (Box A 50)
      Groundbreaking, 1974 September 27, and Dedication, 1976 April 6. (LSR Album Accession number 135.)
    - 400-22, National Park Service ceremony, with Lady Bird Johnson and military honor guard, 1976; Color snapshots (Box A 50)
      LSR Album Accession number 136. LBJ Memorial Grove? Also includes Evening Star, and construction in Caribbean?
    - 400-23, Dedication of the Bench in Memory of Alexander Russell, Princeton University, 1977 July 28; Black and white 8x10 in magnetic album; some deterioration of pages. Loose color photo in back pocket. (Box A 48)
      Brooke Astor, LSR. (LSR Album Accession number 137.)
    - 400-24, Dedication of Abby Rockefeller Mauze Pavilion at MSKCC, 1977 November 30; 8x10 color prints (Box A 51)
      Facilities and patients. (LSR Album Accession number 138.)
    - 400-25, Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Service, New York University, 1978 September 13; Album in slip case. Includes audiotape. Black and white and color prints (Box A 52)
      Presentation album for LSR, who spoke at the service. Includes LSR, MFR, Richard Nixon. Audio cassette tape included with album, along with acknowledgement note from Mrs. Elmer Holmes Bobst. (LSR Album Accession number 139.)
    - 400-26, United Hospital Fund 100th Anniversary, 1978 October 9; 8x10 color prints by Murray Garber; binder mislabeled 1976 (Box A 53)
      Mrs. George M. Billings and LSR honorees. (LSR Album Accession number 188.)
    - 400-27, Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government (SUNY), 1980s; 8x10 black and white prints (Box A 52)
      Dedication. LSR, MFR, Happy, DR around plaque. (LSR Album Accession number 140.)
    - 400-28, The "Black Butte Dedication" Special, 1979 September 30 - October 5; Color snapshots 3x5 with captions, itinerary, menus, clippings, etc. Magnetic album. (Box A 54)
      Presentation album for LSR and MFR. Departure on Union Pacific train from Seattle to Black Butte surface coal mine in Wyoming. (LSR Album Accession number 141.)
    - 400-29, Construction, Museum of Modern Art Tower, West 54th Street, 1983; Color snapshots (Box A 55)
      LSR Album Accession number 181.
    - 400-30, Presentation album to LSR on his retirement as Chair of the Board of Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1985 June 4; Color 8x10 photos (Box A 55)
      Historic and publicity photos. JDR Jr. and AAR, LSR, NAR, Lady Bird. Not about LSR retirement. (LSR Album Accession number 217.)
    - 400-31, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, Photographs, 1960-1987; Full 3-ring binder with vinyl pageholders - some rumpled. Combination of 8x10 black and white photos and folders with clippings, programs, and brochures (Box A 56)
      Photographs and printed materials concerning LSR and MSKCC: Rockefeller Research Laboratories, MSKCC-RU Scholars Residence, Centennial Convocation, LSR Honorary Chairmanship, LSR and Paul Marks Presidency, Frank Sinatra Concerts, Dedication of Memorial Hospital, Mary Lasker tribute, Dedication of Outpatient Building, 75th Anniversary of Memorial Hospital. (LSR Album Accession number 230.)
    - 400-32, President and Mrs. Reagan's Visit to Pocantico (Kykuit); Statue of Liberty Centennial Celebration, 1986 July; Color snapshots of event; sticky spill on album pages (Box A 57)
      LSR Album Accession number 231.
    - 400-(32.1), President and Mrs. Reagan's visit to Pocantico (Kykuit); LSR and MFR at White House with Ronald and Nancy Reagan, 1986 (Box A 57)
      Album includes copy of thank you letter from Reagan to DR, July 10, 1986. MFR on crutches.
    - 400-33, Dedication of Rockefeller Research Laboratories at MSKCC, 1989 May; Photos and printed addresses; interleaved letters of congratulations from George Bush and Ed Koch. Enclosed in Paul Marks to MFR and LSR, August 22, 1989. (Box A 58)
      Includes dedication of LSR Board Room, May 11, and Frontiers of Cancer Research Symposium, May 16-17. (LSR Album Accession number 239.)
    - 400-34, Fundacion Luis Munoz Marin (San Juan, PR), 1990; 12 8x10 color prints in ringbound album (Box A 58)
      LSR-MFR visit; album sent February 9, 1990, by the executive director. (LSR Album Accession number 240.)
  - 500 - Travel, 1954 - 1980s; 6
    Albums within the 500, Travel, series are grouped by geographic location: E = Europe, M = Mexico, U = United States. In addition, V= Vessels.
    - 500-E1,Norway, On board ship, 1974 (Box A 59)
      Sea Star (LSR Album Accession number 147.)
    - 500-E2, "Princess", 1975 May; Magnetic album, sticky spill on edges of pages, but pages and 8x10 photos intact (Box A 59)
      Barge trip in France with Heiskells et al. (LSR Album Accession number 142.)
    - 500-E3, Greece, 1979 (Box A 60)
      LSR Album Accession number 145.
    - 500-E4, Greece, Italy, England, 1982 (Box A 60)
      Maze's, England. (LSR Album Accession number 144.)
    - 500-E5, France; Catskills, 1982 (Box A 61)
      Rodin Museum, Giverny, Maze family (England?); Catskills visit. (LSR Album Accession number 197.)
    - 500-E6, Maze family, 1983 (Box A 61)
      England. Paintings, LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 90.)
    - 500-E7, England and France, 1984 May; 4x6 color snapshots in magnetic album. Some photos slipping (Box A 62)
      London changing of guards; Mill Cottage, Jessie Maze, interiors, paintings, and gardens; France, Paris, vineyards, cathedral. (LSR Album Accession number 143.)
    - 500-E8, Mary and Laurance Rockefeller Annual "Birthday" Trip, 1987 May 5-19; 4x6 color snapshots (Box A 62)
      Burie, Cognac, Colmar, Hintersarten, Baden-Baden. Includes Schweitzer Museum. MFR, LSR, and sights. (LSR Album Accession number 238.)
    - 500-M1, San Miguel Allende, 1981 - 1982 February (?); 4x6 color snapshots. Envelope with additional prints (dated March 1982) taped to inside cover (Box A 63)
      LSR, MFR, and Rutherfords. Album M2L (or M1.1) a nearly exact duplicate of this album, except for a few pictures. (LSR Album Accession number 148.)
    - 500-M1.1, San Miguel with Rutherfords, 1982 February; 3 x 5 color snapshots in a 12 x 6 album. (Box A 63)
      Album is labeled on the inside cover "San Miguel Allende, February, 1982," with the notation "500-M2 L." With a few variations, however, the album is a duplicate of album 500-M1, and they are grouped together for that reason. ((LSR Album Accession number 148.1.)
    - 500-M2, San Miguel, 1982 (Box A 64)
      With Rutherfords. (LSR Album Accession number 149.)
    - 500-M3, San Miguel, 1983 (Box A 64)
      With Rutherfords. (LSR Album Accession number 150.)
    - 500-M4, San Miguel, 1984 (Box A 65)
      LSR Album Accession number 151.
    - 500-M5, Mexican trip with Rutherfords, 1985 February 28 - March 17 (Box A 65)
      LSR Album Accession number 152.
    - 500-M6, San Miguel, 1985 (Box A 66)
      With Rutherfords. (LSR Album Accession number 222.)
    - 500-M7, Mexican trip with Rutherfords, 1985 February 28 - March 17; Album pages coming apart (Box A 66)
      Marked as "LSR's book." (LSR Album Accession number 223.)
    - 500-M (unnumbered) San Miguel de Allende, circa 1986; color snapshots, large magnetic album. No labeling or identification of album. (Box A 67)
      LSR, MFR, Rutherfords
    - 500-S1, Cia Anma Firestone Venezolana, Caracas, 1954 February 10; 8x10 black and white photos in presentation album. Back cover is detached. (Box A 67)
      Mr. and Mrs. Roger Firestone, Mr. and Mrs. Henry G. Weilert, LSR and MFR, and others at reception and tour of Firestone plant. LSR carrying camera on tour. (LSR Album Accession number 155.)
    - 500-U1, St. John (Caneel Bay), 1960s (Box A 68)
      NAR, Happy, LSR, MFR. Photographs by Miles Raymond. (LSR Album Accession number 160.)
    - 500-U2, St. John (Caneel Bay), 1960s (Box A 68)
      NAR, Happy, LSR, MFR. Photographs by Miles Raymond (same occasion as album 160). (LSR Album Accession number 161.)
    - 500-U3, Larry Rockefeller Alaska Trip, 1963 (Box A 69)
      LSR Album Accession number 156.
    - 500-U4, Caneel Bay, 1968 December - 1972 August; Album of flip stacked photos - coming unglued (Box A 69)
      Also JY with Albright, Chorley, family; some photos of Pocantico. (LSR Album Accession number 192.)
    - 500-U5, 1970s (Box A 70)
      Greece, 1979; Union Pacific train (Black Butte trip), Indian museum, construction site. (LSR Album Accession number 198.)
    - 500-U6, 1980s (Box A 70)
      Japan; Woodstock (LSR Album Accession number 159.)
    - 500-U7, 1980s (Box A 70)
      California or Hawaii; Maryland? (LSR Album Accession number 157.)
    - 500-U8, 1980s (Box A 70)
      Unidentified couple with LSR and MFR. Flowers and grounds - Florida, circa 1980. (LSR Album Accession number 158.)
    - 500-U9, Virgin Gorda, 1980s; 3x5 snapshots in magnetic album. Some photos slipping. (Box A 70)
      LSR, MFR, Wes Frye and others. Shopping, sailing, at Little Dix, at Sandy Cay, flowers. (LSR Album Accession number 163.)
    - 500-V1,Sea Star, 1970s; Professional 5x7 photos; black and white and color. (Box A 71)
      Christening and launching; interiors, deck, and profile. (LSR Album Accession number 165.)
    - 500-V2, Sea Star Serenity (January 31-February 6), 1970s; 3 x 5 color snapshots glued 4 to page; some black and white. (Box A 71)
      Album tracing voyage (Antigua-St. Croix), inscribed "To Mary and Laurance with great thanks from (Olive and Tom). Includes Little Dix. MFR, LSR, and guests. MFR on crutches. LSR in red and yellow print pants. Some photos added later. (LSR Album Accession number 162.)
    - 500-V3, Sea Star, 1970 Christmas (Box A 72)
      Caribbean. (LSR Album Accession number 196.)
    - 500-V4, Sea Star, 1971; 11 photos, on acidic paper (Box A 72)
      Album presented to LSR and MFR by Andrew and Marian Heiskell. (LSR Album Accession number 164.)
    - 500-V5, Sea Star, Norway, 1974; Oversized album with embossed cover.Mainly 5 x7 color photos of the trip. Photos slipping on pages. (Box A 73)
      LSR, MFR trip with Floyd and Kime Hall. Christmas thank you note from Halls to LSR and MFR enclosed. (LSR Album Accession number 166.)
  - 600 - Resorts, 1936-1988; 7
    Albums within the 600, Resorts, series are grouped by resort name or geographic area: B = Boulders, Ca = Caneel Bay, D = Dorado Beach, L = Little Dix Bay, M = Mauna Kea, S = St. Croix, We = West Indies.
    - 600-B1, Boulders, 1985 March; 3x5 snapshots in magnetic ringbound album; some photo slippage (Box A 74)
      Grounds, buildings, landscape, golf course. MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 167.)
    - 600-Ca-1, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1956-1960; 8x10 black and white photos glued to highly acidic album pages - pages crumblng. Album disbound and digitized. (Box A 75)
      Restricted - Material has been digitized. Access to the paper album is restricted.
      Scrapbook album of professional and artistic photographs of scenes of Caneel Bay and St. John. (LSR Album Accession number 174.)
    - 600-D1,Dorado Beach Hotel, 1978 June; 8x10 color prints in leather DBH album (Box A 74)
      Facilities, grounds, flowers. Professional PR type photos. (LSR Album Accession number 173.)
    - 600-L1, Little Dix Bay, 1964 January 17-20; Color 3x5 snapshots glued in. (Box A 76)
      Dedication. Snapshots on board ship (large sailboat) and Lady Caneel; and at Little Dix; incl. LSR and MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 176.)
    - 600-L2, Little Dix Bay, 1966 May; Approximately 6x9 color photos, glued to pages; album's plastic spiral binding is breaking (Box A 76)
      Grounds, facilities, interiors, mechanicals, landscaping. Professional photos. (LSR Album Accession number 177.)
    - 600-L3, Little Dix Bay, 1964; Black and white 8x10 in spiral bound album - not on accession number list? Some loose photos and drawings tucked under front cover flap (Box A 76)
      Construction, models, and Opening; LSR and others. (LSR Album Accession number unknown.)
    - 600-L (unnumbered), Visit of Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II to Little Dix Bay, 1966 February 23; 8x10 black and white photos glued to pages (Box A 77)
      Formal album with photos and photocopied clippings.
    - 600-M1, Mauna Kea, 1960s-1970s; No text, but not really a photo album (Box A 78)
      Bound volume of printed photos of hotel interiors. (LSR Album Accession number 172.)
    - 600-M2, Golf Tournament at Mauna Kea, 1960s-1970s; Black and white 8x10 prints. Ringbound album, covers detaching. (Box A 78)
      Album of photos by O. J. Noer, "For Mr. L. Rockefeller." (LSR Album Accession number 171.)
    - 600-M3, Mauna Kea and other, 1968 October - [1972]; Magnetic album, 3x3 color snapshots, coming loose from pages (Box A 78)
      LSR Album Accession number 170. Also includes LBJ(?) and redwoods?; Wyoming and JY; Christmas; Sea Star?, NAR; Caribbean.
    - 600-M4, Mauna Kea, 1960s-1970s; Color snapshots; some have identifications on back. Some mylar pages stuck together at inside seam; some photos partially stuck on one edge to album adhesive; has some odor. (Box A 79)
      LSR Album Accession number 169.
    - 600-M5, Mauna Kea, 1977 October; 14 color 3x5 snapshots (Box A 79)
      Public relations photos. Artwork, grounds, guests (general). (LSR Album Accession number 168.)
    - 600-M6, Mauna Lani, 1983; Color 3x5 snapshots. Adhesive on binding beginning to deteriorate - leaving residue on photos (Box A 79)
      Dedication. LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 195.)
    - 600-M7, Mauna Kea and MFR, 1988 January; color 4x6 snapshots, 3 ring album (Box A 80)
      MFR, flowers, landscape, artwork. (LSR Album Accession number 237.)
    - 600-S1, St. Croix Property, 1978 June; Color 8x10 photos in leather album. (Box A 81)
      Professional photos of property, golf course, and St. Croix sites. (LSR Album Accession number 178.)
    - 600-We-1, West Indies Company Pictures of Caneel Bay Plantation, 1936-1938; Black and white 3x5 and 4x8 shots of grounds, boats, people. (Box A 81)
      Pictures of Caneel Bay Plantation (under the management of the West Indies Company in St. Thomas), taken between 1935 and 1938 by Dr. George H. Knight, who presented the set to Allston Boyer in June 1959. (LSR Album Accession number 179.)
- Small, 1940-1989; 2
  - 000 - Art, 1980s; 1
    - 000-1, Art: Indian pottery and baskets, 1982 June; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Posters in background. (LSR Album Accession number 28.)
    - 000-2, Kent House, circa 1982; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Pocantico, NY. Art work, pool, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 31.)